Tether, for example,
last year, we
last year,
believe delivered $50
delivered $50
million per employee.
million per
That is
unheard of.
But we think
that the capitalizing
the capitalizing
on all of
these new technologies
new technologies
is going to
drive productivity gains
drive productivity
much higher than
much higher
people can even
postulate right now.
postulate right
And with that,
while many people
many people
are afraid, given
the robotics movement
robotics movement
and AI,
everyone being
thrown out of
thrown out
jobs, we disagree.
We think this
We think
is going to
be one of
the greatest opportunities
greatest opportunities
for the
entrepreneurial spirit
in history, especially
because you can
history, especially
go to ChatGPT
or Grok and
to ChatGPT
say, "I think
there's a huge
there's a
unmet need for
unmet need
this, that,
or the other
product or service."
product or
Think about it.
Think about
And I would
like to start
I would
that business. Boy,
when we started
business. Boy,
Ark, I would
have loved to
have loved
have a starting
point like that.
point like
And you can
work with ChatGPT,
with ChatGPT,
xAI, Grok to
xAI, Grok
build your business.
Try it. If
you're looking for
you're looking
a job,